Hello everyone. Welcome back to NFA
Live. Thank you for joining and
apologies for the slightly delayed
start. There were some audio issues at
Rob's end and he has I wouldn't say rage
quit, but uh
he's
he's decided I think the the technical
issues are a little a little a little
too much to deal with today. So it's
just Ben and myself, but Ben, how are
you? Lovely to see you.
>> Doing great. How about you?
>> I'm okay, thanks. I'm okay.
Before we before we were became on you
were talking about you're you're going
to New Zealand next month.
>> Yeah.
Yeah, it's it's crazy cuz it is next
month. It's like in
6 weeks or something. Maybe five five to
six weeks. I'm speaking at a at a
conference there. A tech conference
actually. It's not a crypto conference.
Okay. I've always wanted to go, so
that'll be kind of cool.
>> Nice. Where whereabouts in New Zealand
is it?
>> Christchurch.
>> Christchurch. Okay.
>> Yeah. So the Southern Island.
>> Yeah. Do you Have you Have you any idea
how long that's going to take you? Is
there a direct flight from your corner
of the world or is it about 17
17 different ones?
>> There's a
it's going to be a There's going to be
more than one stop. I think I I think
it's going to take two stops to get
there. No, maybe even
one two Yeah, I think there might be two
stops before we before we get to the
final destination.
>> Okay.
>> So three three flights total.
>> And that well that's just to get there.
>> That's just to get there, yeah.
>> Wow, I hope it's I hope it's worthwhile.
I hope it's uh
>> Yeah, I think it will be. I mean I've
always wanted to go to New Zealand, so
it's a good opportunity to go.
>> Yeah, it does does it does sound like an
amazing place. And Kiwis are generally
in my experience some of the nicest
people you'll ever encounter. So, you
know, it's apparently just a country
full of extremely nice [clears throat]
and pleasant people.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, just a shame about the neighbors,
as they say. But, there we are. Okay,
great. Well, in
now that I've now that I've managed to
insult one half of Australasia and play
praise the other,
let's let's crack on. So, we we were
going to in the absence of Rob, Ben, I
thought we could talk a little bit about
SpaceX. I'd love to get your thoughts on
that. Um
I'd like to get your thoughts on
situational awareness. Are you aware of
this the aware the the hedge fund the AI
hedge fund that blew up? And I thought
we could also talk about the the cold
card exploit. Um
you posted a really good tweet
about that a few days ago, which I will
I will get up later on. But,
yeah, I feel I for me this is sort of
one of the worst things to happen in
crypto for a very long time. Um so, I
thought we could talk about that and and
then see how we go. And I also want to
ask you a football, sorry, soccer
related question as well. So,
>> call it we can call it football tonight.
>> Okay, we're all friends here.
Um okay, well, firstly, I'd I'd be
interested to get your thoughts on
SpaceX. I know we've sort of talked
about SpaceX and Elon Musk a bit before,
but um
it reported its first earnings as a
public company
the other day.
And they were a massive
they were it was a good earnings report.
They beat expectations, but the scare
around the sort of capex commitment
actually sent SpaceX shares lower. And
obviously,
SpaceX has been, you know, suffering on
that front, you know, since not long
after it went public. And this seems to
be a bit of a trend with these
hyperscaler earnings. You know,
expectations are now so high that
they're sort of selling off despite some
actually quite strong figures. So, I
just interested to get your thoughts on
what do you make of SpaceX at this point
in time and do you think um you know, do
you think it's going to take a lot more
than a decent earnings report for for
the stock to sort of start ticking back
up or
>> Well, I mean I think like, you know,
like a lot of IPOs when they first
launched they're typically there's this
excitement, there's some, you know,
overvaluation there. Even when Tesla
launched, you know, and I I talked about
this when the SpaceX IPO occurred, when
Tesla launched it rallied like 50, 60%
and then kind of was weak for the rest
of the midterm uh for the rest of that
midterm year. They actually launched in
the same month. I I believe both the
SpaceX IPO and the Tesla IPO launched in
June of midterm years, uh I believe. Um
so, maybe uh maybe Elon Musk is is in on
the 4-year cycle, too. I don't know, but
um it uh
I I think it sort of as you get later in
the cycle
you start and instead of just rewarding
good earnings reports, you also want to
see like what are the future commitments
and if that's going to start to degrade
at all because no one really knows who
the winners of the AI race is going to
be. Um
So, I I think there's a lot going on
with that. I you know, you have I think
you had a lot of like stock lockups that
were un sort of unlocking around this
time and that'll continue for a while.
You know, you had the hype with the
SpaceX launch. I I I think this is just
like a a digestion phase after an IPO
launch, which is what we see with a lot
of IPO launches. In fact, I I believe it
was
it was out if you look at like Warren
Buffett and um that crew, I'm pretty
sure they made a comment about how they
hadn't bought an IPO since the 1950s or
something or or it's just a really,
really long time
because often times IPOs will initially
go up, get everyone to come in, and then
they'll go down for a little bit and
then you get sort of the real price
discovery that occurs after the hype
wears off. We saw that with Tesla. We
also saw it with Apple. I mean when that
when Apple launched it sort of surged
initially and then faded, didn't really
go anywhere for a couple of years and
then now look at Apple. So I I think
what you're seeing is is fairly normal.
I mean now listen with SpaceX coming in
with evaluation it came in at I mean it
was fairly high.
Um
So I don't think people should expect
SpaceX stock to like you know go up 100x
anytime soon [clears throat]
like what we saw with uh
you know with Tesla.
But I'm long-term bullish on SpaceX. You
know and and I
one of the reasons is I'm just bullish
on Elon Musk long-term and I don't want
to bet against him.
Um You know I think I think the SpaceX
stock could stay you know somewhat
subdued for the rest of the year.
But long-term you know I I think being
bullish on this stuff is better than
being bearish even though the short-term
you know obviously has been bearish. So
that's my view on it. I I think that
long-term SpaceX as we get you know more
into space and as that race picks up in
the coming decades I think that SpaceX
will have
a leg up on their competition. It's just
going to take a while to get there right
like anything. The technology is like
you can kind of see where we're headed
but our our imaginations get ahead of of
reality sometimes but normally reality
catches up.
>> Yeah. Yeah, it's yeah but it's just a
lot of patience and those those
other examples that you cited are you
know a a good ones aren't they cuz it
just shows that you know there is a lot
a lot of hype around a stock early but
you know long-term these things build if
these companies build things that people
want then you know they will perform but
it's not I guess maybe people in crypto
are sort of so used to something going
parabolic out of the gates.
Right. They assume that that that that
filters through to the real world. I do
I find it kind of kind of interesting at
the moment that SpaceX is sort of so
focused on
AI. You know, a lot of these concerns
around the expenditure, you know,
because it's spending so so much on AI,
which I guess makes sense in in the fact
that, you know, AI is just where it's at
right now. But as you kind of alluded
to, I think it I think it kind of make
for me it's certainly a much more
interesting stock in terms of like what
it could actually do in space. I mean, I
think the AI angle is
seems to me to be a little bit
peripheral to its kind of long-term uh
long-term value proposition. You know,
this could be this could be the company
with a with you know, a massive monopoly
um on you know, on everything everything
beyond Earth, which is
pretty huge, really.
>> Yeah. I mean, I I know people are like,
well, the the valuation is really high
and egregious, but but there's also the
the reality that money's never going to
stop being printed. So, theoretically,
the companies that are are providing
value for society, as long as they keep
printing money, like those companies
will probably keep doing well.
Um who knows? [clears throat] Maybe in
in you know, 10 or 20 years we'll be
talking about how the new companies on
the block are are coming out at 10
trillion dollar valuations and how crazy
that sound. I mean, it all sounds crazy
in the time and then you look back 20
years later and you're like, oh, well,
this is just normal. Um
that's why we invest, because of
inflation, right? If it I mean, that's
what a big reason why I invest is
because if you don't invest inflation
will eat you alive.
>> Yeah. Yeah, you've got to you've got to
take the take your chances out there in
the in in the deep waters of the market.
Um yeah, lots of speculation in the
comments about how how low it could go.
I mean, I would I would certainly be
interested in it below $100, but as you
say, it could um it could stay it could
stay below that and you know for quite a
while as as you say. And patient you
know the patient ones will be the ones
who win out.
Um okay, let's let's talk a bit about
did did you follow this
I want to say situation this this
business with situational awareness this
hedge fund that AI hedge fund that went
spectacularly bust? Was that on your
radar last week?
>> It was. I I was actually yeah I was
following it somewhat. But you know what
it reminds me of? It reminds me of the
saying we've we've talked about a few
times on here. There's a difference
between being right and making money,
right? Like the guy he's been right. I
mean it's not like AI it's not like the
AI bets haven't been great, but there's
a difference between being right and
making money and
this is a good example of that. Now I
don't I don't think he's going to give
up. I mean there's in throughout all of
history there's so many examples of
hedge funds and and different funds that
have blown up and people lost a lot of
money, but yet the person running the
hedge fund or running that specific fund
um ended up just raising more money and
and going right back at it. And and then
potentially becoming successful, right?
I mean he's young too.
Uh a lot of these people are going to
make these mistakes. It's unfortunate
that for him it had to be such a big
mistake um because like the mistake he
made is not that dissimilar from the
mistake that everyone makes, you know,
trading any market. It's just that the
scale at which he got to was a lot
different. But I think you could argue
that that when you go through that it
does make a better investor out of you.
And so you know, I I I have a feeling
that he still has um a career ahead of
him. Is is as crazy as that might sound
to some people. I think that I think
there's a lot of people that are like
no, if you make one mistake you're
you're done forever. No one you know, no
one cares about it anymore. Like you you
all your future opinions are null and
void.
Um at least that's how people treat me
sometimes when I guess I'm wrong.
So I I think that long-term
um you know, he'll probably come back. I
think I already saw that he was coming
back and he like raised several hundred
million dollars for something.
Um
But yeah, no, I mean I I I think it also
shows that you know, there's a lot of
leverage in the system as well and and
it it it won't I mean it doesn't take
much to completely flush things out,
right? And you know, I talked before
about a correction in stocks that will
likely start probably like in September.
We've seen it in the last three midterm
years. We've seen it um occur in two of
those Septembers. One time it started in
August.
And you know, the sort of the consensus
I've seen in in some of the comments are
like, well, you know, how could that
happen? You know, AI is still
doing great. And I agree. Like I mean AI
I mean I use AI every day, right? Like I
use it all the time. My employees use it
all the time. When my if my employees
are not using AI, I get irritated that
they're not because um because they're
just more productive when they use it,
you know?
So there's not but but again, there's
there was nothing wrong with AI
necessarily last month and you still got
a correction. So um I I think there's
you know, there's certainly leverage in
the system. Maybe maybe what we saw is
kind of a warning shot for for a deeper
correction
uh in in a couple of months or
something. Kind of in in line with what
we've seen in the prior uh three midterm
years. But I mean those are my views. I
I What what happened with Helm is
it happens a lot and that doesn't mean
it's the end end for Helm and his
career. It just means that you know,
sucks. It's I mean I mean the Was
Citadel Was it Citadel that came in and
bought it up?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I mean it's great for them, you
know? I mean it's uh
It's a doggy dog world, you know? You
you um
Yeah, I mean that's what that's the
world we live in and and I don't you
don't hate the player, hate the game.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I thought that was quite an
interesting dynamic to the whole thing.
Uh the fact that you know, this as As
pointed out, this guy was so young. I
mean, I think he only left college two
or three years ago. You know, he's he's
he's really you know, really at the
beginning of his career.
>> Right.
>> And then, you know, someone
it was almost like revenge of the
boomers, wasn't it? It's like Ken
Griffin who's, you know, been around the
block many, many times. You know, has to
sort of come in and go, "Look, you know,
we'll take it from here." But, I think
you're right in that, you know, I I
I think I, like many people, was sort of
a bit quick to write this guy off this
this Leopold guy off cuz you read the
headlines and you think, "Wow, that is
such a lot of money to lose." And
obviously, yeah, you know,
it was a winning trade, but he
over-leveraged himself, you know, what a
what a what a foolish thing to do.
But then, I think you're right. Like,
you know, this is the sort of thing that
forges you know, experience is so
important, isn't it? And so many
successful entrepreneurs, you know, it's
very easy to look at them and think that
they succeeded first time. And actually,
a lot of them you dig into their stories
and some of them have just you know, a
whole strings of failures behind them.
You know, either company either you
know, things that went completely bust
or never got anywhere or sort of managed
to run up and eventually failed, you
know, so many successful people have
failed
often multiple times. And actually, you
know, you think this guy's probably this
guy has learned a very difficult lesson,
but he's learned it probably at the
right time when
you kind of feel like the AI AI as an
industry is still kind of getting
started.
>> Um
>> Yeah, and by the way, we all make this I
mean, like if if you or I given up on
what we wanted to do anytime we ever
made a mistake, I mean, like think about
how silly that would have been, right?
Like
>> I mean, I feel like no matter what
industry you go in, no matter what you
do, you will fail at certain times. And
it's about how you respond to that
failure.
I feel like that defines us, not the
failure itself. I mean, I've I've failed
many times, but um
I mean, it it just sucks for him cuz
it's on such a a grander stage and like
everyone knows about it, right? It's not
like It's not like he just did it in his
basement and like he's the only one who
knows about it. Um
everyone knows about it. That's the
But, I mean, you could argue that
that'll that'll make him into a a better
trader in the future. I at least
hopefully. I mean, hopefully it does.
There's no guarantee that it does, but
I'd like to think that he could learn
from his mistakes.
>> Yeah, hopefully he doesn't go go on to
make even bigger mistakes, you know,
what he lost a 10 billion this time, you
know, next time he loses 100 billion.
>> Yeah.
>> Um no, I'm sure I'm sure it'll make him
uh you know, make him a better make him
a better investor overall. It's It's
interesting, isn't it? Because, you
know, the AI trade has failures like
this. Um crypto had its own version and
unfortunately, that was that involved a
lot more criminality in that and Sam
Bankman-Fried and
he's currently paying for that mistake
with 25 years, but um it's uh
>> [laughter]
>> I saw someone post about that, too, and
they were like, you know, as crazy as it
sounds, if if Sam Bankman-Fried were to
ever if he were to get like pardoned or
whatever
um and came back, he probably would be
able to raise a ton of money, too. And I
was like,
man, you're probably right.
>> Yeah, I think definitely. I think
definitely it's sort of like you just
think one day this guy this guy will be
back and at it again and will people be
like, "Shut up and take my money."
Um it's crazy, but yeah, what a story.
Um
Okay, I want to talk about um I want to
get your thoughts on another story now
and this one I feel is one that's a lot
harder to
harder to laugh about and this is the
exploit of the Coldcard wallets. Um so,
for people unfamiliar, these uh Coldcard
is a hardware wallet solution. It's a
Bitcoin only
uh hardware wallet and uh uh, the um an
exploit was uh, an exploit was um,
uh,
done on it and I think using AI. I think
um, I think there's a lot of talk that
AI was used to find this legacy bug and
exploit. I think the random random
number function uh, in these wallets and
basically a lot of people who, as you
pointed out in a tweet Ben, a lot of
people who thought that they were doing
the right thing, you know, who were
doing everything that they've been told
to do,
i.e. keep your Bitcoin keep the keys to
your Bitcoin offline in cold storage.
Um, and a lot of people ended up losing
it. Um, and yeah, I mean a hundred well
north of a hundred million dollars of
Bitcoin uh, has been lost so far. Um,
it's prompted a lot of soul searching
within the industry. Interestingly as
well,
it the the impact of it wasn't really
seen in the chart. So, I just wanted to
get your thoughts on on that really. And
I mean, for me, I I see this as possibly
you know, one I I I tweeted about this
and I said I think this is kind of this
is the worst thing to happen to crypto
since the 10th of October. And I think
you could make a case for it being worse
than that because cold there's something
something sanctified, you know, the idea
of cold storage has been
you know, has been really badly damaged.
I mean, do you does that sound like
hyperbole to you or do you think this is
as really as serious as that?
>> I mean, I would say fundamentally this
is worse. Um, I mean, you know, the 10th
of October
was only bad because
there was very little liquidity in a lot
of altcoins
on a lot of the exchanges. But, if you
think about it like on the 10th of
October,
at least from open to close, Bitcoin
only dropped 7%. Like, which was not a
huge drop. It was just that I think it
exposed the weakness that was in the
altcoin market. But, we had been
covering this for years that the
weakness in the altcoin market was there
the entire time. And and the only reason
it wasn't exposed was because Bitcoin
was in a bull market. But, you know, you
can look at Bitcoin dominance the entire
2023, 2024, 2025. Bitcoin dominance is
going up the entire time. Um and then by
the way, this is what happened in 2019
as well during higher interest rates and
and quantitative tightening. When QT
ends, you know, Bitcoin tops out before
QT ends and then it immediately exposes
the weakness in the altcoin market that
was always there. So, I I mean, for me,
the weakness in the altcoin market was
uh it it it's been there for years and
it took Bitcoin going into a bear market
to immediately expose that weakness.
But, this with the Coldcard stuff,
this is one of those things where you
have a lot of people that thought they
were doing the right thing, but uh and
this is not really a failure of Bitcoin.
It it's, you know, and and I think
people should be aware of that. It's
this implementation by this other party
um and and them not
them not doing what they should be
doing, right? I mean, if if you're going
to if you're not going to take security
seriously and I mean, I think I even
read the source code, part of it, in the
comments and they even talked I believe
they mentioned in the comments that like
they probably what they were looking at
wasn't necessarily ideal and and perhaps
they should change it later. I can't
remember if that was for this one or
something else, but
um
I mean, it's just unfortunate, you know,
it it's unfortunate and I I think people
that have probably never looked up
entropy for Bitcoin before now have been
Googling it a lot recently.
And it it just sucks because now,
you know, it's hard to What do you tell
those people? Because like they didn't
buy the ETFs, they didn't keep their
crypto on exchanges,
but yet they still ended up
losing their Bitcoin.
And I think as an industry,
it sets us back, right? Like it's going
to set us back. Again,
why should this midterm year be any
different than every other midterm year,
right? Like there's always it sets us
back, it makes the industry look bad.
Um
And people are not going to
differentiate between,
you know, Bitcoin and the wallet they
use to hold their Bitcoin. They're just
going to think the whole thing is a
scam. You know, I'm not saying everyone,
but I guarantee you there are people
that spent the last several several
years stacking Bitcoin,
and now it's gone. And well, you know, I
honestly if if that were me,
um
like I don't know what I'd do, but I I'd
say there's a good chance I would I
would just start putting money
elsewhere, right? And not worry about it
anymore. Cuz I was looking at this, you
know, unfortunately Bitcoin Bitcoin's at
the same valuation against the S&P
that it was at 5 years ago, right? Maybe
even almost 6 years ago.
And so,
you've taken on a lot more risk with
this security, you know, these security
issues and and holding your, you know,
holding the keys to your Bitcoin, or do
you keep it on an exchange? Do you buy
the ether But you still haven't even
outperformed the S&P 500. So, there's a
lot of people that are going to come to
that realization, and then
that's going to be that. Now, again, we
are coming up near the end of the
midterm year, so theoretically,
assuming this time is not different,
Bitcoin should bottom soon as well.
But a lot of times these events happen
in the midterm year, and then it causes
sort of a a capitulation.
And and then that capitulation is from
the events of of that occurred
throughout the year. People are selling
cuz they're just giving up, and then you
finally start your next bull market.
Um
As far as the price,
a a lot of times in the summer of
midterm years, like Bitcoin is doing
exactly what it's doing now, where it
just kind of bounces around, doesn't
really do anything, but retail interest
slowly fades. And then by the end of the
year, there's basically no retail
interest anymore. Um you get your final
drop, it scares people, it wakes people
back up, and then the next bull market
starts. That's how every single bear
market is has occurred. And you know, in
2022, it was FTX. In 2018, we had that
massive like 50% drop at the end of the
year.
And and I I can't I don't know what this
one's going to be. I mean, maybe we
won't have one, but I would guess
there's going to be something, and that
something will be blamed on whatever's
occurring at the time. But I think you
could argue it's kind of a culmination
of of things that have been going on the
entire year. Because I mean, we've also
saw we've seen issues with stretch, as
well. Um you know, it's back up a lot,
but
there's definitely people that have lost
some confidence. Having like, you know?
Uh so, I I think there's a lot of
things, and and you and and look, the
S&P keeps going to new all-time highs.
So, it's not enough to just say
Bitcoin's not breaking down. It's also
not breaking up, either, right? Like,
while everything else,
you know, while indexes and stuff are
going to new highs, Bitcoin's just
sitting humdrum at 60K. And so, you
know, you you could argue it is having
an effect on the price. It's just not
outright capitulation, at least not yet.
>> Yeah. It's committing if you like, it's
committing that sort of cardinal sin of
not doing anything, you know? It The
only thing worse than not going up is is
not going down.
>> Right? I mean, yeah. I mean, it's it's a
tough market, and I people are getting
impatient.
Um
it's probably going to continue.
>> Yeah. And and and I think that's an
interesting interesting word to use, as
well, impatient. You know, because
and that kind of for me, that kind of
goes back to what's
to what's so sad about this cold card
thing is that so many of these people
would have gone like, okay, I don't you
know, I'm not a trader. I'm not
interested in, you know, in trying to in
in trying to sort of play around with my
Bitcoin and sell it high and buy it back
low, or whatever it was, whatever it is.
I just want to hold it for my future,
for my kids' future, whatever that might
be, you know, to protect against
inflation, to have to have
self-sovereign control over my assets,
whatever it might be.
And
and, you know, to to then have it stolen
out from underneath them is just you
know, yeah, as you said, I don't if I
was in that position, I don't know how I
would feel, but I mean, I I I can
imagine that I would be very tempted to
sort of throw in the towel with Bitcoin,
with with with crypto in in total
because
it feels like something something
fundamental has been violated. And yeah,
it's it's a terrible thing. And we just
got to hope I mean, there were some
interesting there were some interesting
takes on it on Twitter as there always
are. Quite a few people pointed out that
Coldcard is a relatively is a very small
group of people.
Um
I think I heard it described it by some
as a sort of rinky-dink outfit based in
you know, out of Canada or something
like that. Whereas some of these other
hardware wallet solutions, you know, the
likes of Trezor or Ledger, etc. are
much, much bigger and much better
resourced, etc. etc. But as you kind of
as you I think touched on earlier, you
know, for people outside of crypto,
they're not going to make that
distinction. That for now, whenever we
talk about self-custody, we can no
longer say that it has a spotless record
when it comes to hacks and exploits. I
mean, people have
um you know, people have lost their
keys. There've been sort of user errors
in the past, which have never been you
know, a good look and never been a good
advert for holding Bitcoin or or for,
you know, crypto in general. But that's
always been their problem. That's always
been because they screwed up.
But now, whenever we have that
conversation about self-custody, there
will always be this, you know, footnote,
caveat, whatever it is, you know,
Coldcard
uh got exploited in in summer 2026 and a
bunch of people lost a lot of money. You
know, some of and and you know, these
were people in who had in many cases had
been holding Bitcoin for a really long
time.
Um
So, yeah. It is it is real I I think
sets us back years is is exactly is
exactly the point. And I think until
really there there is a more
user-friendly and
I suppose foolproof solution to this,
then it's going to be very hard to say
to people, you know, well, if you want
to buy Bitcoin, just buy the ETFs.
You know, and again, that was that was
that was one of the that was one of the
big reactions that I saw to this thing.
It was like a bunch of people saying,
well,
you know, the BlackRock wouldn't have
lost it. So, why shouldn't I just buy
that?
>> Well, and it's also hard to be like, you
know, if people are want to get into
Bitcoin, it's hard to be like, well, you
got to do all this due diligence. I
mean, a lot of people don't know how to
check like whether this stuff would have
been Like it's easy it's easy for a few
like hardcore Bitcoin maxis that have
been here for 15 years to be like, well,
you know, you should have known or you
should have done your due diligence. But
the reality is it's like
99.9999%
of people like can't do that. Like and
they won't do that.
Uh
>> Yeah.
>> So, it I mean, it it leaves the industry
kind of in a peculiar position, I I
guess.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I yeah, either can't do it
or or won't do it or don't have the time
and it's just yeah, you know, one of the
one of the ways that traditional
banking, for instance, has has made you
know, this is something I come up
against again and again or certainly
when when more people were asking me
about crypto.
You know, people are so used to
convenience. People are so used to their
banking apps
uh working seamlessly. They're so used
to not having to worry, you know, okay,
if their if their bank is hacked or
whatever, then they'll get the money
back. You know, they're used to things
like Was it FDIC insurance? Um
you know, you're insured up to a certain
Your money's insured by the by the
federal government.
Um and telling people that you can you
know, that you've got to forget all
that. No, the the the the Bitcoin
solution is that has got none of that
convenience. And now, unfortunately, you
know, it doesn't have it doesn't have
that safety as well or certainly that's
going to be the perception.
Yeah, it was um it was a real real sort
of a head in hands moment. Um
and I feel yeah, heart goes out to all
the people who who lost Bitcoin in that.
It's it's it's a real tragedy.
Um and I guess the other thing that that
that sprung to mind when thinking about
that was, you know, so many of these
people would have just wanted to park it
and forget about it.
And, you know, not be involved with all
the sort of political side of crypto and
everything that's going on there. And of
course, on that side of things, we have
the Clarity Act as well. Um I think
there's what, 2 days left until the
August recess? Does it start on the 8th?
Um have you got any further thoughts on
Clarity? I mean, do you think that that
it might by some miracle squeeze
through?
>> I have no idea.
Um but I also don't really care about
it. I mean, it was like I it was hard
for me to get excited about a lot of
this stuff this past cycle, like the
ETFs such as future reserves.
I'm just like, you know, this is like
antithetical to Bitcoin. I don't really
care if this stuff happens or not. And I
I think that's kind of just propagated
into the bear market. I I just don't
really care. I mean, for my perspective,
crypto is doing a lot better before
governments got involved.
Um
and you know, like the more the
governments get involved, it almost
feels like the worst crypto has been
doing. I mean, long term, you could
argue that it's all like it's bullish,
but there's like any like any
technology, there's a there's like a
time difference between like you know,
when like expectations and reality,
right? Like a lot of people had
expectations
that, you know, the ETFs would be a game
changer and that the strategic reserve
would be a game changer, but then like
they kind of haven't been, right?
Um this past cycle was
not nearly as good as every other cycle,
right?
Um
And so I I know people keep talking
about the Clarity Act and I remember we
were even talking about it last Q4 and
and you know, we were saying, "Look,
we're probably going into a bear market
and
what will probably be blamed for the
drop in early 2026 is the Clarity Act
not passing." And sure enough, didn't
pass, sure enough, we had a drop, and
sure enough, people blamed that stuff.
And then they started bring blaming Jane
Street. You remember that?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Um no one cares about that anymore, but
that was all everyone cared about back
in like February.
Uh so,
I don't know. Like I don't I honestly
don't follow that stuff because I don't
I don't really care that much about it.
Like I don't I don't I'd I'd rather just
stick to, you know, the cycles and the
charts and and focus on that. And um I
mean, I hope it eventually passes, but
if it didn't pass,
you know, I I don't even think it would
I mean, it I don't think it would be the
end of crypto. I I think it would crypto
would just go down a new path. Um
And again, like I I think back to how
crypto was
in 2013,
2017,
you know, 2020,
and it was basically all before
governments got involved. Like all the
really fun times were before governments
got involved. And now I think like since
they got involved,
crypto's kind of sucked.
So, I don't know. As far as I'm
concerned, I'd rather focus on other
other stuff.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
Absolutely. I I agree. And actually, one
of those other things that um that
you've now got a bit more time to focus
on, Ben, is football. Um because I never
I never actually got your thought cuz
you I I I don't want I'm going dwell too
much back on the World Cup because I
know that's past um past now, but
what was the Argentina game like? You
went to Argentina in the quarterfinal,
right?
>> Argentina Egypt.
>> How was that?
>> It was great. I mean, it was an
incredible game.
I mean, it was controversial
for sure.
I mean, it was, but I'll tell you the
the the energy in the stadium was
insane, you know, like
I mean, I I felt bad. I mean, I I felt
bad for for Egypt that that goal got
called back.
But I also, you know, like I also wanted
to see Messi score. You know, I wanted
to see a lot I mean, it was I I feel
like if I had to go back and look at
if I had to pick like any game to go to
in the entire World Cup, that's got to
be top three, right? Like it was just
one of the most it was one of the
craziest games that occurred. And and
when they played when Argentina played
England, that was also a crazy game.
Like that would have probably been
incredible to be at, too.
Just because of how that played I mean,
it seems like almost every single game
that Argentina had
they came back at the very last minute
and won, you know?
It happened a lot, actually. I mean,
even with even with Cape Verde, right?
Even with Cape Verde, like they they
didn't beat them until
until extra time. They didn't beat Egypt
until the very end of the game. They
didn't beat England until it was like
the very end of the game.
I think there was another I think there
was another close one, too, from what I
remember. I'm just blanking on which
game it was, but yeah, like I I thought
it was a great a great atmosphere. I'm
glad I was able to go. I mean, it
probably won't be in the United States
again for a long time. So, at least not
the men's. I think the women's World Cup
is coming here in
2031, I believe.
>> Okay.
>> I could be wrong.
>> Okay. And actually, I wanted to ask you
as well. This I this was sort of
building up to my main question, which
was more about this um FIFA Forward
Enterprise. Have you been keeping up to
date with this
>> A little bit, yeah.
Yeah, cuz the European they wanted to
commercialize it more and sell the sell
the rights to some private investors.
And uh I know I saw
uh
the European League they came out and
said, "You know what? We won't
participate in the World Cup if this And
then And then other leagues kind of
capped and then a few other leagues kind
of came out in support as well. And now
they've they've sort of taken it back.
But
Yeah, I mean I I guess there's the
there's the there's capitalism and
there's wanting to make money on
literally every little thing, but then
there's also preserving the integrity of
the game. And I I don't blame the soccer
organizations, you know, not wanting to
for the uh
sport as a whole to feel like it's being
sold like the rights are being sold off
to you know, the highest bidder and
stuff. I It's probably for the best. I
mean
we're all human, right? We all are
greedy. So, it's not like I can't
somewhat understand where where where
they're coming from and trying to trying
to to to sell these rights, but I it's
probably not the right move for the you
know, for the integrity of the sport and
the future of of of
uh soccer or as you guys would call it
football.
>> Yeah. Yeah, it's it's prompted Yeah, I
mean um it's it these plans to these
plans to sort of basically commercialize
it. I can tell you they they did not go
down well. They've not been going down
well, you know, virtually virtually
everywhere else. So, that's what That's
why I was kind of interested to get your
you know, your take as an American on
it. But um Yeah, I think you know, the
overwhelming I think the overwhelming
sort of thought is that the that the
World Cup was a huge success. Like and
there's always this thing like before it
happens, I remember it before Qatar and
I remember it before Russia and every
you know, everyone always goes, "Ah,
this is going to be a disaster. You
know, the stadiums aren't ready. They
It's It's all going to be you know, it's
all going to be and then it comes along
and it's actually amazing. You know, the
football everyone forgets about it when
the football starts and you know, the
politics kind of bubbles up bubbles
along underneath but it's really about
the football. Um
but it is but it has prompted a lot of
soul-searching cuz on the one hand, you
know, people are people I think are
quite excited about the fact that it
seems to be really taking off in America
and you know, that's that's sort of
grows the game
but there's sort of real reservations
and that's putting it politely about,
you know, the kind of Americanization of
it because like I don't know if you I
don't know if you guys um
uh heard the discourse around things
like hydration breaks and stuff, you
know.
>> Oh, yeah. I mean, commercial let's call
it what they are, commercial breaks.
I I actually I saw a tweet by someone
and he wrote I can't remember who it was
but he literally tweeted out when when
the United States like won the bid to
host this World Cup, he tweeted out that
when it comes to the United States, they
will they'll separate it into four into
four parts because they will have
commercial breaks.
>> [laughter]
>> Sure enough.
>> Wow. Wow. Yeah, it was um yeah, and it's
it's it's very interesting to see now
how Gianni Infantino who is sort of like
the absolute the absolute Bond villain
of the piece is now sort of desperately
trying to hold on to you know, cuz in
the face of this revolt from everyone
else who's just gone right, this
enough is enough. This is quite
>> By the way, there's a there's a troll in
the comments saying he's tired of soccer
soccer. He goes by digitalasset.news.
You might want to
You might want to take him out.
>> digitalasset.news? Oh, I'll
I'll ban him and
>> Yeah, you got you got to get a
>> God, he's in he's in the stream every
every time just causing trouble that
digitalasset.news.
He's a real He's a real wrong'un.
>> [laughter]
>> Um I believe Digital Asset News will be
at uh the ITC conference in November. Is
that correct?
>> Yep, he will be.
Excited to see him there.
>> We can take him up. We can take up his
behavior with him uh in person.
>> We'll have to do that.
>> He won't He won't be such a big man IRL.
>> [laughter]
>> He is taller than me.
>> He is a very tall guy. Um, now uh I did
want to I did want to just quickly um
What's the couple of questions um that I
wanted to flag? Well, I yeah, a couple
of comments. Better to make the mistake
This is going back to Leopold
Aschenbrenner. Better to make the
mistake at a young age than making that
mistake when you're older and your
opportunities are less.
Very, very true. Um, and quite a few
people like I don't know what your
thoughts on this are, Ben, but um
I mentioned that AI might have been used
uh or suspected of being used in this
cold card attack. I mean
This This surely is going to be a theme
not just in crypto, I think it's fair to
say, but like surely the AI hack thing
is only just getting started, right?
>> Well, yeah, I mean I If you think back
to 2022, it was
Voyager and BlockFi and Celsius and then
it sort of culminated with FTX.
So,
yeah, I mean this is kind of the right
time to start that narrative of what's
it going to be that, you know, you also
have um
you also have other things, right?
Um
that are that are going on. It's not
just the whole AI stuff. You also have
BIP 110 um
that's, you know, causing some some
controversy as well. So, I mean there's
a lot of different stuff uh that that,
you know, you we we might be able to You
also have treasury companies that that
look a little, you know, a little uh
little sketch at some point. So,
I don't know what it's going to be, but
you you've got to believe I mean I got
to believe there's going to be something
that's going to make this cycle look
exactly the same as every other cycle
and I just don't know what narrative is
going to be a science. I don't and we'll
I will probably find out in the next 2
months but I don't know what it's going
to be.
>> Yeah. Yeah, we will
we will see. It'll always it's always a
always a surprise not always a pleasant
one. Um okay Ben, I'm going to let you
go there cuz I think we've we've gone
for long enough. Thank you for Thank you
for answering for both Rob and yourself
today.
>> Yep. Yep, so I guess you can say that
all my answers represent Rob's answers
too, right Rob?
>> Yeah, he if he's not here as a as a fan
comments he he can't he can't defend
himself but
yeah, I'll leave you I'll leave you guys
with this thought. I don't want to
finish on too bearish a note but all
this Bitcoin drama not looking good for
newcomers in the space. I have to say I
I agree with Raymond there. Anyhow,
we will be back next week I believe
unless people are on on holiday or
anything and it'll be on your channel,
right Ben?
>> Correct, yep. See you guys next week on
my channel.
>> See you guys next week. Rob, get your
microphone fixed and we'll see you then.
Thanks everyone. Bye-bye.